Another verbal thank you, huh?
شكرًا لفظيًا آخر، أليس كذلك؟
Can't you give a more practical reward?
ألا يمكنك أن تقدم مكافأة عملية أكثر من ذلك؟
Who says I can't?
من قال أنني لا أستطيع؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
This is your reward.
هذه مكافأتك.
Don't overthink it.
لا تفكر كثيرا في الأمر.
I'm fair with rewards and punishments.
أنا عادل مع المكافآت والعقوبات.
I just don't want to owe you a favor.
أنا فقط لا أريد أن أدين لك بمعروف.
I'm not overthinking.
أنا لا أفكر كثيرا.
I was just thinking, since you're so fair,
كنت أفكر فقط، بما أنك عادلة جدًا،
can you give me the reward for collecting the debt last time too?
هل يمكنك أن تعطيني مكافأة تحصيل الدين في المرة الأخيرة أيضًا؟
How should I reward you?
كيف أكافئك؟
I have a face too, you know.
لدي وجه أيضًا، كما تعلم.
Keep dreaming.
استمر بالحلم.
Why did An'an just pass out?
لماذا فقد أنان وعيه للتو؟
Don't tell me that's all she can drink.
لا تخبرني أن هذا كل ما تستطيع شربه.
Fifteen, twenty.
خمسة عشر، عشرون.
Ten, twenty.
عشرة، عشرون.
Stop talking, come on.
توقف عن الكلام، هيا.
Drink.
شرب.
My head hurts so much.
رأسي يؤلمني كثيرا.
Who told you to drink so much yesterday?
من قال لك أن تشرب الكثير بالأمس؟
No one could stop you.
لا أحد يستطيع إيقافك.
Stop drinking that.
توقف عن شرب هذا.
Drink this honey water.
اشرب هذا الماء بالعسل.
Wasn't that to help you vent your anger?
ألم يكن هذا لمساعدتك على تنفيس غضبك؟
That Gao Qing even said you were marrying up.
حتى أن جاو تشينغ قال أنك ستتزوج من رجل أكبر منك سناً.
I can't stand hearing that.
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل سماع ذلك.
They're siblings, after all.
إنهم أشقاء، بعد كل شيء.
It's normal for a younger sister to speak up for her brother.
من الطبيعي أن تتحدث الأخت الصغرى نيابة عن أخيها.
But I really didn't expect this.
ولكنني لم أتوقع هذا حقًا.
What's written in these documents is actually true.
ما هو مكتوب في هذه الوثائق هو الحقيقة فعلا.
Could it be that we were just overthinking it?
هل يمكن أن يكون السبب هو أننا كنا نفكر في الأمر أكثر من اللازم؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Could it be that Gao Xing is just an ordinary person?
هل يمكن أن يكون غاو شينغ مجرد شخص عادي؟
The facts are right in front of us.
الحقائق موجودة أمامنا مباشرة.
We have no choice but to believe it.
ليس لدينا خيار سوى أن نصدق ذلك.
Then how do we explain what happened before?
فكيف نفسر ما حدث من قبل؟
Maybe it was just a coincidence.
ربما كانت مجرد مصادفة.
Maybe it was luck.
ربما كان حظا.
I still can't figure it out.
لا أستطيع أن أفهم ذلك حتى الآن.
Alright, let's not think about it for now.
حسنًا، دعنا لا نفكر في هذا الأمر الآن.
Now the company has funding.
الآن الشركة لديها التمويل.
And we have the Immortal Doctor's secret recipe.
ولدينا الوصفة السرية للطبيب الخالد.
Let's focus and get ready for the next new product.
دعونا نركز ونستعد للمنتج الجديد القادم.
Okay.
تمام.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Qingyan, after all, I am your fourth uncle.
تشينغيان، بعد كل شيء، أنا عمك الرابع.
All these years, I've worked diligently at Qingmu.
لقد عملت بجد في تشينجمو طوال هذه السنوات.
Even if I haven't made great contributions, I've at least worked hard for the company.
حتى لو لم أقدم مساهمات كبيرة، فقد عملت بجد من أجل الشركة على الأقل.
You can't just fire me like this.
لا يمكنك طردني بهذه الطريقة.
What you've done is illegal.
ما فعلته غير قانوني.
Do you know that?
هل تعلم ذلك؟
I know, I know.
أنا أعلم، أنا أعلم.
If it weren't for the fact that you're my fourth uncle,
لو لم تكن أنت عمي الرابع،
I would have called the police long ago.
كنت سأتصل بالشرطة منذ زمن طويل.
I'm giving you the chance to resign yourself.
أنا أعطيك الفرصة للاستقالة.
It's to let you keep some dignity.
إن الأمر يتعلق بالحفاظ على بعض كرامتك.
Get out.
اخرج.
Qingyan.
تشينغيان.
If you don't leave now, I'll call security.
إذا لم تغادر الآن، سأتصل بالأمن.
You—
أنت-
Oh, President Su,
أوه، الرئيس سو،
please don't be angry.
من فضلك لا تغضب.
You should think of a solution.
ينبغي عليك أن تفكر في حل.
If you get fired,
إذا تم طردك من العمل،
then I'll be the next one.
إذن سأكون التالي.
What can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
Su Qingyan doesn't even care about my status as her fourth uncle.
حتى أن سو تشينغيان لا تهتم بوضعي كعمها الرابع.
She fires people without hesitation.
إنها تطرد الناس دون تردد.
She's completely cold and heartless.
إنها باردة تماما ولا قلب لها.
It's all that kid Gao's fault.
كل هذا بسبب الطفل جاو.
If it weren't for him,
لو لم يكن هو،
my position as vice president would be secure.
سيكون منصبي كنائب للرئيس آمنًا.
There wouldn't be so many problems.
لن يكون هناك الكثير من المشاكل.
I have to get revenge for this.
يجب علي أن أنتقم لهذا.
So what are you planning to do?
إذن ماذا تخطط للقيام به؟
What to do...
ما يجب القيام به...
How...
كيف...
Ah!
اه!
Ah, darling,
اه يا عزيزتي
I need your help with this.
أحتاج إلى مساعدتك في هذا.
Me?
أنا؟
Let's use a honey trap.
دعونا نستخدم مصيدة العسل.
That kid Gao only got promoted
هذا الطفل جاو حصل على ترقية فقط
because of Su Qingyan.
بسبب سو تشينغيان.
You go seduce him.
أنت تذهب لإغوائه.
Invite him to a hotel and drug him.
ادعوه إلى فندق وأعطوه مخدرًا.
Then we'll find another woman
ثم سنجد امرأة أخرى
and put the two of them together.
ووضع الاثنين معًا.
We'll take photos of all their embarrassing moments.
سوف نلتقط صورًا لجميع لحظاتهم المحرجة.
Then send them to the company.
ثم أرسلهم إلى الشركة.
By then,
بحلول ذلك الوقت،
Su Qingyan definitely won't keep him.
بالتأكيد لن تحتفظ به سو تشينغيان.
And Su Qingyan
وسو تشينغيان
will become the biggest joke in the company.
ستصبح أكبر نكتة في الشركة.
Director Gao
المخرج جاو
Secretary Xu, do you need something?
السيد السكرتير شو، هل تحتاج إلى شيء؟
What, I can't come to you if there's nothing important?
ماذا، لا أستطيع المجيء إليك إذا لم يكن هناك شيء مهم؟
Last time, you were so close with me.
في المرة الماضية، كنت قريبًا جدًا مني.
Why are you suddenly so distant?
لماذا أصبحت فجأة بعيدة هكذا؟
I'll get hurt, you know.
سوف أتعرض للأذى، كما تعلم.
Don't be like this.
لا تكن هكذا.
There are so many people in the company.
هناك الكثير من الناس في الشركة.
It would be awkward if someone saw us.
سيكون الأمر محرجًا إذا رآنا أحد.
So you mean,
فهل تقصد؟
it would be more convenient if we went somewhere no one could see us?
هل سيكون من الأفضل لو ذهبنا إلى مكان لا يستطيع أحد رؤيتنا؟
The two of us like this
نحن الاثنان نحب هذا
isn't appropriate.
ليس مناسبا.
What's inappropriate about it?
ما هو غير المناسب في ذلك؟
You're the deputy director.
أنت نائب المدير.
I'm the deputy director's secretary.
أنا سكرتير نائب المدير.
If there's work, the secretary handles it.
إذا كان هناك عمل، فالسكرتيرة تتعامل معه.
If there's nothing,
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء،
Director Gao,
المخرج قاو،
are you free tonight?
هل أنت متفرغ الليلة؟
Let's go to a hotel.
دعنا نذهب إلى الفندق.
I want to ask for your guidance on work.
أريد أن أطلب منك التوجيه بشأن العمل.
Guidance on work, right?
التوجيه بشأن العمل، أليس كذلك؟
I'm free, of course I'm free.
أنا حر، بالطبع أنا حر.
Then tonight at seven, Yunlan Hotel.
ثم الليلة الساعة السابعة، فندق يونلان.
Let's not leave until we meet.
لا نترك بعضنا حتى نلتقي.
Gao Xing and Xu Qian
جاو شينغ وشو تشيان
How could that be?
كيف يمكن أن يكون ذلك؟
Did you see it wrong?
هل رأيت ذلك خطأ؟
I saw it with my own eyes.
لقد رأيته بأم عيني.
How could I have seen it wrong?
كيف يمكن أن أرى ذلك خطأ؟
The two of them were flirting in the break room, making eyes at each other.
كان الاثنان يتغازلان في غرفة الاستراحة، ويتبادلان النظرات.
They even said they were going to get a hotel room tonight.
حتى أنهم قالوا أنهم سيحصلون على غرفة في الفندق الليلة.
Get a hotel room?
احصل على غرفة فندقية؟
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
He just recently with me—
لقد كان معي مؤخرًا
With you?
معك؟
Ah.
اه.
Ah, it's nothing.
اه، لا شيء.
I mean, Gao Xing's taste shouldn't be interested in her, right?
أعني، ذوق جاو شينغ لا ينبغي أن يكون مهتمًا بها، أليس كذلك؟
Qing Yan, you really need to be more careful.
تشينغ يان، عليك حقًا أن تكون أكثر حذرًا.
Men these days aren't any good.
الرجال في هذه الأيام ليسوا جيدين.
Xu Qian just has to crook her finger,
كل ما على Xu Qian فعله هو تحريك إصبعها،
and he takes the bait and comes running.
ويأخذ الطُعم ويأتي راكضًا.
If you don't believe me,
إذا كنت لا تصدقني،
go ask him yourself tonight.
اذهب واسأله بنفسك الليلة.
See if he'll tell you the truth.
انظر هل سيخبرك الحقيقة؟
Fine.
بخير.
I'll ask him myself.
سأسأله بنفسي.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
See?
يرى؟
I told you I wasn't lying.
لقد قلت لك أنني لم أكذب.
He really did show up for the date.
لقد ظهر بالفعل في الموعد.
Let's see what he has to say for himself.
دعونا نرى ماذا سيقول عن نفسه.
Don't rush, wait a bit longer.
لا تستعجل، انتظر لفترة أطول قليلاً.
Let's catch him red-handed first.
دعونا نلقي القبض عليه متلبسا أولا.
Gao Xing, you really are something.
جاو شينغ، أنت حقا شيء ما.
You went behind my back and even got handsy with someone else.
لقد ذهبت خلف ظهري وحتى مارست الجنس مع شخص آخر.
And to think I even promised you a reward.
وأظن أنني وعدتك بمكافأة.
Ugh.
آه.
A reward?
مكافأة؟
What reward?
ما هي المكافأة؟
Oh.
أوه.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
I mean, guys like him deserve to be struck by lightning.
أعني أن الرجال مثله يستحقون أن يصابوا بالصاعقة.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
But Qingyan, are you jealous?
ولكن تشينغيان، هل أنت غيور؟
No, why would I be jealous?
لا، لماذا أكون غيور؟
He and I are just contract spouses.
أنا وهو مجرد زوجين بموجب عقد.
He can do whatever he wants.
بإمكانه أن يفعل ما يشاء.
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
They've left, hurry.
لقد غادروا، أسرعوا.
Over there.
هناك.
Excuse me, please.
إسمح لي، من فضلك.
Secretary Xu, your outfit tonight...
السكرتيرة شو، ملابسك الليلة...
...is truly irresistible.
...لا يقاوم حقًا.
Mr. Gao, you're secretly dating her.
السيد جاو، أنت تواعدها سراً.
If President Su finds out,
إذا اكتشف الرئيس سو ذلك،
won't she be angry?
هل لن تغضب؟
Su Qingyan is nothing.
سو تشينغيان ليس شيئا.
Just a little girl.
مجرد فتاة صغيرة.
Compared to a beauty like you,
مقارنة بجمال مثلك،
she's not even worthy to carry your shoes.
إنها لا تستحق حتى أن تحمل حذائك.
Gao Xing is going too far.
جاو شينغ يذهب بعيدًا جدًا.
It's more than just too far.
إنه أكثر من مجرد مسافة بعيدة.
It's downright shameless.
إنه أمر وقح تماما.
I, Su Qingyan, must have been blind to be with—
أنا، سو تشينغيان، لا بد أنني كنت أعمى لأكون مع—
Why are you looking at me?
لماذا تنظر إلي؟
I'm not jealous.
أنا لا أغار.
The night is short.
الليل قصير.
Let's get started.
دعونا نبدأ.
Mr. Gao, don't rush.
السيد جاو، لا تتعجل.
It's our first date.
إنه موعدنا الأول.
We should build some feelings first.
ينبغي علينا أن نبني بعض المشاعر أولاً.
Come on, let's have a drink first.
هيا، دعنا نتناول مشروبًا أولًا.
This wine...
هذا النبيذ...
...is a bit strong.
...قوية بعض الشيء.
There's something even stronger coming up.
هناك شيء أقوى قادم.
Wait here for me.
انتظرني هنا.
I'll go prepare a surprise for you.
سأذهب لأعد لك مفاجأة.
Hurry, hurry!
اسرع اسرع!
Where is he? Where did he go?
أين هو؟ أين ذهب؟
So, I already did as you instructed.
لذا، لقد فعلت بالفعل كما أرشدتني.
I made him drink the wine.
لقد جعلته يشرب الخمر.
Sit, sit, sit.
اجلس، اجلس، اجلس.
Sit.
يجلس.
Baby, look.
حبيبتي، أنظري.
Gao has already fallen into the trap.
لقد وقع جاو بالفعل في الفخ.
Where are the people you arranged?
أين الأشخاص الذين قمت بترتيبهم؟
Don't worry, they'll be here soon.
لا تقلق، سوف يكونون هنا قريبا.
Gaoxing, explain this to me clearly.
قاوشينغ، اشرح لي هذا بوضوح.
Let go of me! What are you doing?
دعني أذهب! ماذا تفعل؟
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
There's surveillance.
هناك مراقبة.
Your fourth uncle drugged me.
عمك الرابع أعطاني المخدر.
And set up surveillance too.
وأنشأوا المراقبة أيضًا.
It's right behind.
إنه خلفك مباشرة.
It's recording right now.
يتم التسجيل الآن.
So what do we do now?
فماذا نفعل الآن؟
You act with me.
أنت تتصرف معي.
Act?
يمثل؟